Did you ever just have the idea?
The path to financial freedom,
then it died in an AI chat box.
because you didn't have the means to push it through and see it live?
Or is the projects section on your résumé looking a little...
rough?
And you're tired of all those
'thanks for your application'
emails?
Introducing...
Spitch.
It's a way to broadcast your idea, get visibility, partnerships and collaborations.
Pitch it in less than a minute, post it, and people swipe right or left, based on what they see, to connect with you and push it forward.
Pitchers and builders, those with the means and those with the skills,
connecting for the price of a coffee.
The market starts here, at uOttawa.
I'm a fourth-year engineering student. I live this problem.
If you think this would make a great LinkedIn post, let's chat.
Or swipe right.